{
  "parsed": {
    "education": [
      [
        "Education",
        ""
      ]
    ],
    "experience": [
      [
        "experience",
        " in innovation, business and product"
      ],
      [
        "experience",
        ", managing development schedules, developing"
      ],
      [
        "Experience",
        ""
      ],
      [
        "Experience",
        ""
      ]
    ],
    "skills": [
      [
        "skills",
        " in Swedish,"
      ]
    ],
    "raw_text_preview": "Velde Vainio\nEspoo, Finland\nvvainio@gmail.com · +358405174642\nlinkedin.com/in/veldevainio\nProfessional Summary\nSolution-oriented professional with substantial experience in innovation, business and product\ndevelopment, project management, software development, go-to-market planning and execution,\nand strategic management.\nIn-depth expertise working with customers to understand requirements, developing high-level\nsystem architecture, defining user experience, managing development schedules, developing\ngo-to-market plans, and executing strategy.\nHistory of providing leadership in business intelligence and information technology solutions,\nmarketing, finance, administration.\nArticulate communicator with proficiency in Finnish and English. Basic skills in Swedish,\nGerman and Spanish.\nCore Competencies\nDeveloping and managing digital transformation and accelerated innovation.\nFull stack software development, lean methodology, architecting, machine learning and AI.\nEnd-to-end marketing for b..."
  },
  "anonymized_text": "<PERSON>, <LOCATION>\n<EMAIL_ADDRESS> · <PHONE_NUMBER>\n<URL>\nProfessional Summary\nSolution-oriented professional with substantial <IN_PAN> in <IN_PAN>, business and product\ndevelopment, project <IN_PAN>, software development, go<IN_PAN> planning and execution,\nand strategic <IN_PAN>.\nIn-depth expertise working with customers to <IN_PAN> requirements, <IN_PAN>\nsystem architecture, defining user <IN_PAN>, managing development schedules, <IN_PAN>\ngo<IN_PAN> plans, and executing strategy.\nHistory of providing <IN_PAN> in business intelligence and information <IN_PAN> solutions,\nmarketing, finance, administration.\n<IN_PAN> communicator with proficiency in <NRP> and English. Basic skills in <NRP>,\n<NRP> and Spanish.\nCore Competencies\n<IN_PAN> and managing digital transformation and accelerated <IN_PAN>.\nFull stack software development, lean methodology, architecting, machine learning and <LOCATION>.\n<IN_PAN> marketing for both traditional and new media.\nEducation\nMaster of Science - Major in International Design Business <IN_PAN> (IDBM)\nAalto <IN_PAN>, <LOCATION>, <DATE_TIME> – <DATE_TIME>\nBachelor of Communication (Business) - Major in Marketing and Advertising\nBond <IN_PAN>, <LOCATION>, <DATE_TIME> – 2005\n<IN_PAN>\nAWS Cloud <IN_PAN> Professional Certificate\n<PERSON>, certificate earned at <DATE_TIME>\nMachine Learning Specialization by Stanford <IN_PAN> & <URL>\n<PERSON>, certificate earned at <DATE_TIME>\nPrompt Engineering Specialization by <IN_PAN>\nCoursera, certificate earned at <DATE_TIME>\nContinued…\n<IN_PAN>\nOivan / NXme FZ LLC, <LOCATION>, <LOCATION>\nPrincipal <IN_PAN>, <DATE_TIME> – 2022\n<IN_PAN> and proposing software solutions for <IN_PAN> agencies, anticipating and defining\nproject requirements, and implementing suitable solutions based on clients' needs.\n▪ Evaluated and developed eCommerce solutions for a <NRP> <IN_PAN> agency.\nIdeant dmcc, <LOCATION>, UAE - Ideant Ltd, <LOCATION>, <LOCATION>\nFounder, CEO, <DATE_TIME> – <DATE_TIME>\n<NRP> and captured various business opportunities across <LOCATION> and <LOCATION> within\ndesign and manufacturing, sustainable energy, and <IN_PAN>.\n▪ Developed and launched a location-based app for <IN_PAN> environmental health impact.\nAUA Industria Ltd., <LOCATION>, <LOCATION>\nChief Inventor, <DATE_TIME>\nDevised and <IN_PAN> new types of simple and reliable road security barriers for the <NRP>\nand global markets.\n▪ Inventor, designer and project manager for setting up the <IN_PAN> and assembly, as well as\ndefining the business model for selling the security barriers.\nF-Secure Corporation, <LOCATION>, <LOCATION>\nBusiness Development Manager, <IN_PAN> & New Concepts, <DATE_TIME> – <DATE_TIME>\nExamined market segments and <IN_PAN> landscape to capture new business\nopportunities. <PERSON> contract preparations for mergers and for signing up business partners.\n▪ Created and launched new services and products, identifying future business areas and\nmanaging outsourcing partnerships.\nF-Secure Corporation, <LOCATION>, <LOCATION>\nMarketing Program Manager, Direct Consumer Business, <DATE_TIME> – <DATE_TIME>\nLed global marketing program for security software, executing several global product launches\nacross diverse sales channels, managing creative agencies to develop marketing communications.\n▪ Designed, planned and executed several large marketing campaigns with cutting edge\nproduct packaging and both online and offline marketing communication and materials\nF-Secure Corporation, <LOCATION>, <LOCATION>\nProject Manager / Development Manager, <IN_PAN> R&D, <DATE_TIME> – <DATE_TIME>\nManaged key development projects and quality assurance of the company’s flagship product line.\n<IN_PAN> <IN_PAN>\nProtomo business incubator for startup entrepreneurs, <DATE_TIME>\nAsio Data, Ltd. & Logos Test Engineering, Ltd., Software Engineer, <DATE_TIME> – <DATE_TIME>\n"
}